[
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What controls the Lungs?",
    "options": {
      "a": "the heart",
      "b": "the spleen",
      "c": "the kidney"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "A muscle is contracted and has constricted blood flow. How might the skin feel in that area?",
    "options": {
      "a": "cool",
      "b": "flaccid",
      "c": "warm"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What type or category does tapping and hacking fall into?",
    "options": {
      "a": "petrissage",
      "b": "friction",
      "c": "tapotement"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "tapotement"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Which neurotransmitter is released at the neuromuscular junction?",
    "options": {
      "a": "acetylcholine",
      "b": "seratonin",
      "c": "epiniphrin"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "How do you put the hamstrings on the slack?",
    "options": {
      "a": "client prone with bolster under the ankles",
      "b": "client prone with bolster under the hips",
      "c": "client supine with bolster under the ankles a. client prone with bolster under the ankles"
    },
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "A client has low back pain. What do you do?",
    "options": {
      "a": "give them aspirin",
      "b": "position them prone with a bolster under the hips",
      "c": "position them prone with a bolster under the chest - b. position them prone with a bolster under the hips"
    },
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Which is a saddle joint?",
    "options": {
      "a": "acromioclavicular joint",
      "b": "first carpometacarpal joint carpometacarpal joint"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": "first carpometacarpal joint"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "If there is pain with active movement, but not with passive movement, what does this probably indicate?",
    "options": {
      "a": "a joint/ligament issue",
      "b": "a muscle/tendon issue issue"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": "a muscle/tendon issue"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Which of these does NOT adduct?",
    "options": {
      "a": "gracilis",
      "b": "pec major",
      "c": "latissimus dorsi",
      "d": "soleus"
    },
    "correct_option": "d",
    "correct_answer_text": "soleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "A carpenter has pain around his olecranon process. Which muscle is involved?",
    "options": {
      "a": "biceps brachii",
      "b": "deltoid",
      "c": "triceps brachii"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "triceps brachii"
  }
]